friendstertalk.com 2012-12-31

# FTalk / Privacy Policy

› Ownership of Information  
FTalk.us is the sole owner of all the information collected on the FTalk.us.

› Public Forums  
FTalk.us makes message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

› Cookies  
We use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features.

Our advertisers may use cookies on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. DART cookies may also be used for ad serving through Googleâ€™s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising. This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests. DART uses "non personally identifiable information". You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

› Log Files  
Like most standard web servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

› Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, FTalk.us may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on FTalk.us.

› Links  
The FTalk.us contain links to other sites. Please be aware that FTalk.us is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by FTalk.us.

› Notification of Changes  
Whenever FTalk.us changes its Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate.
